The Plague is a drama, thriller film directed by Charlie Polinger.
A socially awkward tween endures the ruthless hierarchy at a water polo camp,
his anxiety spiraling into psychological turmoil over the summer.
Ben, played by Everett Blunck.
Jake, played by Kayo Martin.
Daddy Wags, played by Joel Edgerton.
Eli, played by Kenny Rasmussen.
Logan, played by Lucas Adler.
Matt, played by Caden Burris.
The Plague is a 2025 psychological drama-thriller film written and
directed by Charlie Polinger in his directorial debut.
It stars Everett Blunck, Kayo Martin, Kenny Rasmussen, and Joel
Edgerton, who is also a producer on the film.
The film had its world premiere at the Un Certain Regard section of the 2025 Cannes Film Festival on May 16, 2025, and was given a
limited theatrical release in the United States on December 24, 2025, and is set to expand nationwide on January 2, 2026.
The film explores themes of summer camp, camp,
water polo, malicious, cautionary.
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.